http://www.vfc.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
What Is Covered In This Privacy Statement?
At VF Corporation, we understand that you care how information about you is collected, used, and shared. This Privacy Statement describes information we may collect about you directly or indirectly, how and why we may collect, use and share your information, and the choices you have regarding your information. As more fully described below, we collect, use and share your information to better serve you and to improve our own business processes. By using our websites, mobile applications, or facilities, or by providing information to us in other ways, you agree to this Privacy Statement. VF Corporation may receive information about you from the brands and companies we own or control (our “subsidiaries”), including Altra®, Bulwark®, Dickies®, Eagle Creek®, Eastpak®, Horace Small®, Icebreaker®, JanSport®, Kipling®, Kodiak®, Liberty®, MakeIt Movement®, Napapijri®, Red Kap®, Smartwool®, Terra®, The North Face®, Timberland®, Vans®, VF Solutions®, Walls®, and Workrite®. We may also provide information about you to our subsidiaries, and when we do, this Privacy Statement also describes how our subsidiaries collect, use and share your information. For purposes of this Privacy Statement, when we use the terms “we,” “us” and “our,” or similar terms, we are referring to VF Corporation and our subsidiaries.
If you are a resident of a state or territory of the United States this Privacy Statement applies to you and your personal information, except for the sections captioned “YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS” and “YOUR NEVADA PRIVACY RIGHTS” unless you are a resident of California or Nevada, respectively.   If you are a resident of the State of California, the section captioned “YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS" applies to you and your personal information. If you are a resident of the State of Nevada, the section of captioned “YOUR NEVADA PRIVACY RIGHTS" applies to you and your personal information.
What Categories of Information About You Are Collected?
In order to help us better understand and serve you, we collect information that identifies you or that we can associate with you (your “personal information”) as well as information that does not identify you (e.g., anonymous or aggregated data), and we may collect various categories of information directly (from you), or indirectly (from third parties), as more fully described below.
Personal Information Collected Directly From Consumers
We really want to know and understand you so that we can give you an excellent customer experience. The categories of information that we have collected directly from consumers during the preceding 12 months include the following: name, nickname/alias, physical or mailing address, unique personal identifier, online identifier/screenname, IP address, email address, account name, driver’s license number, signature, physical characteristics or biometric information (such as size, height, weight or other information relevant to your footwear and apparel preferences), telephone number, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, other payment information, sex or gender, age, products or services purchased or considered, purchasing histories or tendencies, Internet activity (e.g., browsing history, search history, clicks), location data, audio, electronic, visual, thermal, or olfactory information, preferences, behavior, and social media information.
Personal Information Collected Indirectly From Third Parties
We also obtain information about consumers from third parties. The categories of information that we may obtain indirectly about consumers during the preceding 12 months include the following: name, nickname, physical or mailing address, unique personal identifier, online identifier/screenname, IP address, email address, account name, driver’s license number, signature, physical characteristics or biometric information (such as size, height, weight or other information relevant to your footwear and apparel preferences), telephone number, education, employment status/history, insurance information, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, other payment information, race or ethnicity, sex or gender, age, sexual orientation, religion, national origin, products or services purchased or considered, purchasing histories or tendencies, Internet activity (e.g., browsing history, search history, clicks), location data, audio, electronic, visual, thermal, or olfactory information, preferences, psychological traits/ predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities/aptitudes, social media information.
How Information About You Is Collected
We obtain the categories of personal information listed above in the ways described below:
How Personal Information Is Collected Directly From You
When you interact with us, we may collect information about you directly. Examples of direct interaction with us include when you visit our websites, shop in our stores, communicate with our customer service representatives, attend our events, use our mobile applications, participate in our marketing efforts (including contests sweepstakes and virtual events), participate in our customer loyalty programs, or any other way you interact with us. When we collect information about you directly, we may ask you to affirmatively furnish the information to us (such as when we ask you for your telephone number), or we may collect the information from your electronic device (such as when you visit our website) or by observing your activity (such as when you visit our websites).
How Personal Information Is Collected From Third Parties
We may also collect information about you indirectly from third parties. In some cases, we may engage third parties to help us operate our business, and they may collect data on our behalf in the course of the services they provide to us. In other cases, third parties may obtain information about you independently, and we may acquire that data from the third party (for example, by purchasing the data from a data broker).
The following table shows the categories of personal information that we may obtain directly (from consumers), or indirectly (from third parties), by category of source.
Categories of Information We Collect
Information Collected Directly from Consumers
Information Collected from Government Entities and Public Records
Information Collected from Consumer Data Resellers/Brokers
Information Collected from Advertising Networks
Information Collected from Internet Service Providers
Information Collected from Operating Systems and Platforms
Information Collected from Social Networks/Social Media
Name
x
x
x
Internet activity (browsing history, search history, clicks, etc.)
x
x
x
x
Location data
x
x
x
Why Your Information Is Collected and Used
We use the personal information we collect directly and indirectly to conduct our business, communicate with you, and provide better products, services, and experiences, as further described below. The specific purposes for which we or our service providers may collect and use information about you are: (1) to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested; (2) to place, process and ship orders; (3) to send order and shipping confirmations; (4) to enable and improve our customer service; (5) to respond to your comments; (5) to process questions or complaints; (6) to personalize your experiences; (7) to analyze your opinions, preferences and shopping habits; (8) to analyze trends and statistics; (9) to administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions; (10) to analyze and improve our websites, mobile applications, and our products and services; (11) to market our products and services to you, including by sending you marketing communications and other information regarding our products, services, or special events; (12) to share reviews, testimonials, or other user-generated content; (13) to facilitate our merger or acquisition activities; (14) to secure and protect our information and technology systems, as well as information about you and other consumers; (15) to facilitate internal audits, dispute resolution, or investigations; (16) to evaluate new technology for our businesses; (17) to conduct market research; (18) to formulate our business strategies; (19) to analyze business information about organizations to which you may belong (i.e., your employer); (20) to enable us to monitor and evaluate our third party service providers and their activities on our behalf; (21) to manage our gift card program and other stored value programs; (22) to keep records of transactions; (23) to comply with our contractual obligations, including compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards; (24) to detect actual or potential fraud; (25) to establish and maintain data back-ups for our business continuity and disaster recovery; and (26) to comply with various legal obligations to which we are subject. In the following table, we summarize the purposes for which we collect and use each category of personal information:
Categories of Information We Collect
1
2
3
4
5
6
7
x
Internet activity (browsing history, search history, clicks, etc.)
x
x
x
x
x
x
x
x
x
What Information About You Is Shared and With Whom?
We may share some or all of your personal information with our subsidiaries which operate under the following brand names: Altra®, Bulwark®, Dickies®, Eagle Creek®, Eastpak®, Horace Small®, Icebreaker®, JanSport®, Kipling®, Kodiak®, Liberty®, MakeIt Movement®, Napapijri®, Red Kap®, Smartwool®, Terra®, The North Face®, Timberland®, Vans®, VF Solutions®, Walls®, and Workrite®.
We may also share your personal information with service providers who provide services to us or conduct activities on our behalf. When we share your personal information with our service providers, we instruct them to limit their use and further sharing of your personal information so that they only use or share your personal information for the intended purposes and we further instruct them not to sell your personal information. One example of our information sharing with a service provider is when we share your name, address, and similar contact information with a courier service for the purpose of delivering a product to you and notifying you of the status of the shipment. We may also share your information with a third party who is not a service provider and who is not acting on our behalf, and from whom we do not receive compensation, such as our auditing firm.
The categories of information that we may share with a third party (including service providers) for a business purposes, or have shared during the preceding twelve (12) months, includes the following: name, nickname, physical or mailing address, unique personal identifier, online identifier/screenname, IP address, email address, account name, driver’s license number, signature, physical characteristics or biometric information (such as size, height, weight or other information relevant to your footwear and apparel preferences), telephone number, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, other payment information, sex or gender, age, products or services purchased or considered, purchasing histories or tendencies, Internet activity (such as browsing history, search history, clicks, etc.), location data, audio, electronic, visual, thermal, or olfactory information, preferences, behavior, and social media information. We share these categories of information for the same purposes we collect and use them, as described above under the caption “Why Your Information Is Collected and Used.”
We do not sell consumers’ personal information, regardless of their age, and we have not sold consumers’ personal information in the twelve (12) months prior to the date of this Privacy Statement. We do, however, maintain a list of consumers who have notified us that they do not wish for their personal information to be sold. One reason we maintain such a list is because, in the future, we may sell or otherwise divest a brand or business unit, including the customer data associated with that brand or unit, to a company whose privacy policies are different from ours, and we would like to convey the wishes of those consumers to the buyer. To request that your personal information not be sold, please follow this hyperlink: Do Not Sell My Personal Information.
How Can I Opt Out of Online Advertising Or Other Promotional Communications?
Our websites may use cookies or similar technologies to understand more about your interaction with our websites. Our websites currently do not have a mechanism to recognize your Internet browser’s “Do Not Track” signals, but several of the third-party companies who utilize these cookies or other tracking or monitoring mechanisms enable you to opt out of this advertising through mechanisms established by trade groups, as follows: If you wish to reduce this type of third-party interest-based advertising, you may opt out of advertising from members of the National Advertising Initiative here, and from members of the Digital Advertising Alliance here. Please note this does not opt you out of receiving all marketing communications from us. There are other ways in which you can tell us whether or not you want to receive promotional communications from us. When you set-up an account or log into your account on our brands’ websites or mobile applications, you may have an opportunity to make or change your selections with respect to each brand. You also will have an opportunity to opt-out of advertising email messages from us by clicking on an "unsubscribe" hyperlink contained in commercial e-mails those brands send you. If you receive a text message (SMS or MMS) from one of our brands and would like to opt out of receiving further text messages, you may do so by following the opt-out instructions within (or linked from) the text message.
What About the Privacy of Children?
We do not intend to collect personal information from anyone who is under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13 you should not provide any personal information to us. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and suspect he/she has provided personal information to us, you may contact us using one of the Communication Methods described in this Privacy Statement to exercise your rights as a parent or guardian. Because we do not sell personal information, we do not sell the personal information of consumers under 16 years of age.
What Steps Are Taken To Keep Personal Information Secure?
The security of your personal information is important to us. We have instituted reasonable security procedures and measures that are intended to protect your personal information and our information technology systems that store personal information. Unfortunately, no transmission of information over the Internet nor storage of information electronically can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. In order to help protect personal information you provide to us, you: (i) should not share your password or account information with others, (ii) should use a secure internet connection and web browser, (iii) should select a unique, complex, secure password, and (iv) should change your password frequently. If you become aware of any loss, theft, or unauthorized use of a password, please contact us immediately using the contact information below.
What Happens When I Click A Link To Another Web Site?
Our websites and mobile applications may contain links to third-party websites to which this Privacy Statement does not apply ("Linked Websites"). Your use of Linked Websites will be governed by the terms of use, privacy policies, and other terms, notices, and policies set forth on or referenced in those Linked Websites.
What If I Am an International User?
This Privacy Statement describes our policies and procedures in the United States. Regardless of where you live, by using our U.S. website or engaging with us while within the U.S., you consent to have your personal data transferred, processed, and stored in the United States, and allow us to use and collect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Statement. If you live outside the U.S., we may host a website or application designed for use in your jurisdiction, and we encourage you to use that website or application.
YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
This section of our Privacy Statement applies solely to consumers who reside in the State of California.
Your Options Regarding Information About You, and How To Exercise Your Options
Under California law, you have specific rights regarding your personal information. We want to respect your wishes, and we have established processes by which you can exercise your options regarding your personal information. To exercise your options as described in this Privacy Statement, you may contact us in one of four ways:
by telephone at +1-877-709-1800;
by completing the web form at https://www.VFC.com/US-Privacy-Requests;
by mail at: VF Corporation, Attn: VF North America Privacy Program Office, 105 Corporate Center Blvd., Greensboro, North Carolina, USA 27408; or
in person at one of our retail stores in California.
Collectively, these are referred to as the “Communication Methods”. To effectively exercise your privacy options, you must use one of these Communication Methods.
The list below describes the types of requests you may make to us regarding information we have collected from you:
Request to Know: You may ask us to furnish you with (i) the categories and specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you; (ii) the categories of sources from which we collect information about you; (iii) the business or commercial purposes for collecting information about you; and (iv) the categories of third parties with whom we share personal information about you (or have shared in the prior 12 months).
Request to Delete: You may ask us to delete any personal information that we have collected from you and to direct our service providers to delete your personal information from their records. After verifying your request, we will comply as further described below, unless we determine that there is a lawful basis for retaining the information, including because the information is necessary to: (i) complete a transaction or perform a contract between us; (ii) ensure security; (iii) debug or repair errors; (iv) exercise a legal right; (v) comply with another law or a legal obligation; (vi) conduct research; (vii) enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with our consumer’s reasonable expectations; (viii) otherwise use the information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which you provided the information.
Opt-Out of Sale: You may request that we not sell your personal information, if you wish, and we will honor your request. You may make such a request by following this link: Do Not Sell My Personal Information
We will make commercially reasonable efforts to accommodate your request within 45 days; however, we may notify you during the initial 45-day period that we will extend the timeframe by up to 45 additional days, if an extension is reasonably necessary in order to fulfill your request. We will fulfill the same Request to Know from you up to two times in any twelve-month period, but we are not able to fulfill redundant Requests to Know more frequently than that.  We will not discriminate against you because you have made a request described in this Privacy Statement or otherwise exercised your rights under applicable law. We may offer financial incentives or offer you a different price, level, or quality of goods or services in connection with programs that require you to disclose certain personal information, but only if you opt in to such an incentive program. If you opt in to any such incentive program, you make revoke your consent to share your personal information at any time, as described in the terms and conditions of those programs.
In addition, California’s “Shine the Light” law permits customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for the third parties’ own direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us using one of the Communication Methods described in this Privacy Statement, describing your request specifically.
How Will You Verify My Identity?
For your privacy and security, and to prevent fraud and other harmful activities, when we receive a request through one of the Communication Methods, we need to ensure that the person submitting the request is the person they purport to be. Accordingly, we may take reasonable measures to verify the identity of the person submitting the request.  . Initially, we ask you to provide personal information when you submit a request, whether through our web form, toll-free telephone number, mail, or other approved Communication Method. This information will include your first name, middle name, last name, email address, shipping address and telephone number. Providing accurate information that matches our records is necessary so that we can locate the correct information within our systems and service providers, verify the validity of the request, and protect your data.  To verify your request, may ask you to submit evidence proving your identity. You may submit this information simultaneously with your request (by mail or by using our interactive web form) or after your request. The evidence we may request from you, and the degree of certainty we will be required to reach regarding your identity and the authenticity of your request, will depend upon the nature of your request, the nature of the information we have about you, and your ability to furnish information. For requests of specific pieces of personal information about a consumer, we will verify your identity to a reasonably high degree of certainty; whereas for requests to know the categories of personal information collected and used about a consumer, we will verify identity to a reasonable degree of certainty. We may give you options, such as (i) submitting a signed statement and a redacted copy of identifying information (such as a government-issued ID), or (ii) showing your identifying information to our associate at one of our California retail locations.
If we ask you to verify your identity, you must promptly cooperate with our efforts so that we can fulfill your request. If you do not comply, your request cannot be fulfilled; and if you delay in complying, the fulfillment of your request is likely to be delayed, and may be denied, as a result.
What About Requests from Authorized Agents?
If you submit a consumer privacy request on behalf of another person, you will be required to demonstrate your legal authority to act on behalf of that person, and we may contact you for verification purposes. For the protection of our customers, you must furnish all information requested and must demonstrate your authority to our satisfaction before we can fulfill your request.
YOUR NEVADA PRIVACY RIGHTS
If you are a resident of Nevada, you may request that we not sell your personal information in the future, if you wish, by following this link: Do Not Sell My Personal Information.
Changes to This Privacy Statement
We will review our Privacy Statement periodically (at least annually). We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to revise, change, or modify this Privacy Statement at any time.  By engaging with us, including by visiting our website(s), after this Privacy Statement has been updated, you agree to the updated terms of this Privacy Statement.  This Privacy Statement was last updated on July 1, 2020.
